Lokesh Patidar

Full-Stack Developer

- **\(09993977820**
- bansiyalokesh29988@gmail.com
- ▶ Portfolio
- GitHub
- Agar-Malwa, Madhya Pradesh

SUMMARY

Highly motivated IT professional with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, MongoDB, Node.js, and Express.js. Known for strong work ethic, adaptability, and collaborative spirit. Demonstrated ability to excel in team environments while taking initiative to drive projects forward.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development (full time)

Masai School (Coding School) May 2022 – Feb 2023 Bengaluru, India

12th, M.P. Board of secondary Education, Bhopal

Kamla Sagar High School Nalkheda, Madhya Pradesh

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML & CSS | Git | JavaScript
Typescript | Next.js | React.js
Node.js | Express.js | Mongo DB
Chakra UI | Redux / Redux Toolkit
NPM | JWT | Networks calls
Tailwind CSS | Rest API | Sockets

CERTIFICATES

Masai Coding Workshop ☑

Tinder webpage

Zoom marathon challenge 🖸

Masai School

LANGUAGES

English | Hindi

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack (MERN-Stack) Developer

Accpal

Feb 2024 – present

- Contributed to maintenance of Accpal, an accountant software, ensuring stability and reliability.
- Worked on both frontend and backend functionalities.
- Engaged in debugging and troubleshooting to promptly address issues.

Frontend Developer

Dashmed-web

Dec 2023 - Feb 2024 | Remote, India

- Implemented authentication features for Dashmed-web using Next.js.
- Enhanced user authentication flow and experience.

MERN-Stack Developer

Webient Technologies

May 2023 – Nov 2023 | Gurgaon, Haryana

- Crafted robust admin panels for Pink Apron, Ub-Factory, and The St Lucian Hub-HubLA Admin Panel.
- Live streaming application with MERN-Stack.
- Executed significant web3 project with React.js for Bitgert.

PROJECTS

[1] Pink Apron Admin Panel

- Monitor and manage home chefs' profiles, including approvals, updates, and removals.
- Oversee menu listings and updates from home chefs, ensuring accuracy and quality.
- Handle order management, including tracking, status updates, and cancellations.
- Implement and enforce user policies, terms of service, and community guidelines.

[2] Bitgert 🛮

- The real estate marketplace is an online platform.
- It connects clients with realtors, brokers, and property managers.
- It operates as a multi-channel e-commerce platform.
- Tech-Stacks & Tools used: CSS, React.Js, Chakra UI, NPM, Blockchain, Web3, Thirdweb, VS-Code, GitHub.

[3] WebTaskit 🛮

- GitHub Link 🛮
- Collaborated with a team of 5 members to develop a task-tracking website.
- Specialized in implementing robust task management functionality for efficient organization and planning.
- Integrated a calendar feature, enhancing user experience by facilitating event tracking and monthly scheduling.

[4] Pharmeasy 🛮

- GitHub Link 🛮
- Developed Pharmeasy, a consumer healthcare "super app" offering ondemand access to prescription and OTC pharmaceuticals.
- It is a demo project that I worked on with a team of 5 members, utilizing skills that I have learned.

SOFT SKILL

Communication | Teamwork